<resources>
  <string name="app_name" translatable="false">প্রাণিসেবা ভেট</string>
  <string name="enter_your_mobile_number">Enter your mobile number</string>
  <string name="next">Next</string>
  <string name="don_t_have_account_sign_up">Don\'t have account? Sign Up</string>
  <string name="already_registered_login">Already registered? Login</string>
  <string name="submit">Submit</string>
  <string name="name">Name*</string>
  <string name="farmer_name">Farmer Name</string>
  <string name="mobile_number">Mobile Number*</string>
  <string name="email">Email</string>
  <string name="farm_name">Farm Name</string>
  <string name="farm_type">Farm Type</string>
  <string name="number_of_animal">Number of Animal</string>
  <string name="number_of_animals">Number Of Animals</string>
  <string name="address">Address*</string>
  <string name="title_activity_main2">MainActivity2</string>
  <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
  <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
  <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
  <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
  <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
  <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="action_edit">Edit</string>

  <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
  <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
  <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
  <string name="farmer_s_information">Farmer\'s Information:</string>
  <string name="treatment_service">Treatment Service</string>
  <string name="treatment_form">Treatment Form</string>
  <string name="treatment_service_details">
    <![CDATA[
    <p>You can call the hotline number (09643207003) to get
    medical treatment for your animal through the customer service officer or by filling out the
    initial patient information form by yourself. Then you can make payment from your own bKash
    account with the counter number received on your mobile or by clicking on the link received.
    You can pay with the counter number from the personal number of any bKash agent. Our service
    price is Tk.200 per cow / buffalo, Tk.100 per goat / sheep; The service price for each batch of
    chicken, duck, turkey, quail etc. is Tk. 500, dog, cat, rabbit Tk.500 each, birds Tk.100 each
    and other animals Tk.500 each. You can also find out the information of the service from our
    Facebook or website.</p>
    ]]>
  </string>
  <string name="consultancy_service">Consultancy Service</string>
  <string name="consultancy_service_details">
    <![CDATA[
    <p>You can fill and submit the consultancy information
    form yourself from the service receiving form to take the consultancy service of your animal or
    you can fill and submit it through the customer service officer by calling hotline
    (09643207003).Then you can make payment from your bKash / Rocket / Cash or by clicking on the
    link received with the counter number received on your mobile. Or you can make payment with the
    counter number from the personal number of any bKash / rocket / cash agent. Our consultancy
    service prices are divided into two categories, one-time and yearly.</p>
    ]]>
  </string>
  <string name="registered_farm_service">Registered Farm Service</string>
  <string name="registered_farm_service_details">
    <![CDATA[
    <p>The country\'s first government-approved online veterinary hospital has launched a special service called
        \'Registered Farm Services\'. The service will specifically help a farmer to build a profitable farm through
        proper farm management. A farm needs Scientific Housing, Quality Rations, Breeding Decisions / Planning, Green
        Grass Production and Storage, Deworming & Vaccination Scheduling, Farm Daily Activities, Disease Prevention,
        Control and Treatment and Safe & Quality Production and Marketing of Products etc. You can ensure all these
        things through the Farm Registration Services. Proper management is the main directives of the implementation of
        the goals and objectives of the farm. Management is an art or technique that coordinates the farm resources,
        decisions, opportunities and time to make it profitable. We set up a farm mainly for better production.
        Production means milk, meat, eggs,reproduction, and wool. Farm registration to ensure that production!</p> <br>
    <p>Registration Benefits:</p> <br>
    <ol>
        <li>
            &#160;You will get a Vet doctor at your doorstep if needed.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Farm management under the supervision or collaboration by a specific veterinarian each of the month.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;All kinds of planning and management related to the farm will be given from the beginning.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Easy solutions to prevent, treat and manage farm diseases.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;You will get farm planning assistance or science based solutions of current farm.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;You will be able to participate in different training sessions.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Specific specialist doctors (Dairy Consultant, Poultry Consultant, Nutritionist, Reproductive Health
            Specialist etc.) will talk to you every month and supervise the farm.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;For farm management and registration you will get a free mobile app on receiving all farm services.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;You will get ration formulation on the basis of types of animals (cows, goats, layers, cats, etc.), breed,
            age, or stage of animals (calf / kid, calf,milking, weak, sick etc.).
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Get deworming and vaccination schedule at the beginning of the year or when needed.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Get clear advice on breeding planning and reproductive health for farms.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;You will get guidelines and training on grass production / silage making and management.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;You can gain consultation on farm hygiene and biosecurity management.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;You can obtain guidance on smart farm management.
        </li>
    </ol>
    ]]>
  </string>
  <string name="mobile_number_">Mobile Number:</string>
  <string name="name_of_farmer_">Name of Farmer:</string>
  <string name="name_of_farm_">Name of Farm:</string>
  <string name="address_">Address:</string>
  <string name="email_">Email:</string>
  <string name="farm_s_information">Farm\'s Information</string>
  <string name="type_of_farm_">Type of Farm:</string>
  <string name="number_of_animal_">Number of Animal:</string>
  <string name="address_of_farm_">Address of Farm:</string>
  <string name="farm_and_farmer_s_information">Farm and Farmer\'s Information</string>
  <string name="edit_farm_and_farmer_s_information">Edit Farm and Farmer\'s Information</string>
  <string name="service_related_information">Service Related Information</string>
  <string name="service_receiving_form">Service Receiving Form</string>
  <string name="one_time_service">One Time Service</string>
  <string name="payment_form">Payment Form</string>
  <string name="farm_registration">Farm Registration</string>
  <string name="monthly_service_registration">Monthly Service Registration</string>
  <string name="registered_farm_related_information">Registered Farm Related Information</string>
  <string name="monthly_service_related_information">Monthly Service Related Information</string>
  <string name="agent_registration">Agent Registration</string>
  <string name="farm_management_information">Farm Management Information</string>
  <string name="weight_measurement">Weight Measurement</string>
  <string name="hotline_number">Hotline Number</string>
  <string name="treatment">Treatment</string>
  <string name="consultancy">Consultancy</string>
  <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
  <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
  <string name="has_this_animal_been_treated_before_at_ps_vet">Has this animal been treated before
    at pS Vet?*</string>
  <string name="previous_prescription_number">Previous prescription number</string>
  <string name="animal_name_or_id_number">Animal name or ID number</string>
  <string name="select_animal_group">Select animal group*</string>
  <string name="animal_group">Animal group*</string>
  <string name="select_animal_type">Select animal type*</string>
  <string name="animal_type">Animal type*</string>
  <string name="select_animal_breed">Select animal breed</string>
  <string name="animal_breed">Animal breed</string>
  <string name="select_breed_type">Select breed type</string>
  <string name="breed_type">Breed type</string>
  <string name="select_animal_gender">Select animal gender</string>
  <string name="animal_gender">Animal gender*</string>
  <string name="stage_of_male">Stage of male*</string>
  <string name="stage_of_female">Stage of female*</string>
  <string name="is_this_animal_part_of_ps_iot_network">Is this animal part of pS IoT network?*</string>
  <string name="bolus_id">Bolus ID</string>
  <string name="age_of_the_animal">Age of the animal*</string>
  <string name="unit">Unit*</string>
  <string name="weight_of_the_animal_in_kg">Weight of the animal in KG*</string>
  <string name="select_deworming_status_within_the_last">Select deworming status within the last*</string>
  <string name="deworming_status_within_the_last">Deworming status within the last*</string>
  <string name="select_vaccination_status_within_the_last">Select vaccination status within the last*</string>
  <string name="vaccination_status_within_the_last">Vaccination status within the last*</string>
  <string name="type_of_vaccines">Type of vaccines</string>
  <string name="select_the_level_of_temperature">Select the level of temperature*</string>
  <string name="level_of_temperature">Level of temperature*</string>
  <string name="the_level_of_temperature">The level of temperature*</string>
  <string name="temperature_f">Temperature (F)</string>
  <string name="select_the_feed_water_intake_status"><![CDATA[Select the feed & water intake status*]]></string>
  <string name="feed_water_intake_status"><![CDATA[Feed & water intake status*]]></string>
  <string name="select_the_defecation_status">Select the defecation status*</string>
  <string name="defecation_status">Defecation status*</string>
  <string name="select_the_urination_status">Select the urination status</string>
  <string name="urination_status">Urination status</string>
  <string name="select_hair_of_the_animal_s_body_status">Select hair of the animal\'s body status</string>
  <string name="hair_of_the_animal_s_body_status">Hair of the animal\'s body status</string>
  <string name="select_the_salivation_status">Select the salivation status</string>
  <string name="salivation_status">Salivation status</string>
  <string name="select_animal_static_posture_status">Select animal static posture status*</string>
  <string name="animal_static_posture_status">Animal static posture status*</string>
  <string name="select_the_muzzle_status">Select the muzzle status</string>
  <string name="muzzle_status">Muzzle status</string>
  <string name="select_the_sneezing_coughing_status"><![CDATA[Select the sneezing & coughing status]]></string>
  <string name="sneezing_coughing_status"><![CDATA[Sneezing & coughing status]]></string>
  <string name="sweating_status">Sweating status</string>
  <string name="select_the_posture_and_gesture_status">Select the posture and gesture status*</string>
  <string name="posture_and_gesture_status">Posture and gesture status*</string>
  <string name="is_the_illness_happening_for_the_first_time">Is the illness happening for the first time?*</string>
  <string name="was_treatment_sought_elsewhere">Was treatment sought elsewhere?</string>
  <string name="problem_description_in_100_words">Problem description (In 100 words)*</string>
  <string name="are_any_other_animals_affected_by_the_same_disease">Are any other animals affected
    by the same disease?*</string>
  <string name="this_field_is_required">This field is required</string>
  <string name="select_type_of_emergency">Select type of emergency*</string>
  <string name="type_of_emergency">Type of emergency*</string>
  <string name="bangla">বাংলা</string>
  <string name="english">English</string>
  <string name="website">www.pranishebavet.com.bd</string>
  <string name="service_details">Service Details</string>
  <string name="pregnant_cow_care_and_management">Pregnant Cow Care and Management</string>
  <string name="calf_care_and_management">Calf Care and Management</string>
  <string name="daily_activities_of_farm">Daily Activities of Farm</string>
  <string name="importance_of_public_health">Importance of Public Health</string>
  <string name="pregnant_cow_care_and_management_details">
    <![CDATA[
    <p>The care of a cow during pregnancy will depend on the well-being of the calf, milk production, well-being of the
        cow and immunity to postpartum disease. Basically, the care of a pregnant cow needs to be taken specially from
        three months before giving birth, such as a balanced concentration supply, raw grass and adequate supply of hay,
        vitamins and minerals. A healthy mother can give birth to a healthy baby. Therefore, pregnant cows need special
        care to get a healthy calf. The special care of pregnant cows is mentioned below:</p> <br>
    <ol>
        <li>
            &#160;In addition to ensuring adequate and regular balanced concentration feeding for pregnant cows and unborn
            calves, fiber food, vitamins and minerals should be provided.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Milking should be stopped as per proper plan two to three months before the birth of the calf.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Separate accommodation should be provided for pregnant cows, the accommodation must be clean and dry.
            Moreover, dry hay should be spread for sleeping and cows should not be kept in high and low places.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Take regular baths but need to be careful not to feel extra cold or hot to cows. If there is lice or on the
            cow, it should be cleaned.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Necessary measures should be taken to be aware of the time of delivery. In this case, if the cow gives birth
            at night, the farm worker must keep a watchful eye, otherwise the cow may eat the uterus.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;After the onset of calving symptoms, all kinds of preparations need to be done such as disinfection of the
            maternity ward and comfortable environment for the cow.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;After giving birth to the baby, mix Dettol in a little hot water and wash the placenta well with that water.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;The cow should be provided with lukewarm water so that the placenta falls easily to the ground and should be
            buried in the ground as soon as possible as soon as the placenta falls as milk production is severely
            reduced if the cow eats the placenta.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;If the uterus does not fall within 24 hours of giving birth, you should seek the help of a veterinarian.
        </li>
    </ol>
    ]]>
  </string>
  <string name="calf_care_and_management_details">
    <![CDATA[
    <p>Gestational care of calves usually refers to the care of pregnant cows. Milking of pregnant cows should be
        stopped from 3 months before the birth of the calf and at this time the cows should be provided an adequate
        amount of nutritious food. If the delivery is near, the pregnant cow should be kept separate from other cows.
    </p> <br>
    <ol>
        <li>
            &#160;Before the calf is delivered, the calf placement area must be kept clean so that no germs can be
            transmitted.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;The calf should be placed on dry straw or sack immediately after delivery to remove lubricants and blood
            from the nose and mouth.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Arrangements should be made so that the cow can lick and clean the body of the calf. This will not cause
            pneumonia in the calf as well as increase the blood circulation in the body of the calf.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;The calf\'s navel should be cut two inches with a sharp blade or scissors at the time of delivery and then
            apply povicep to that area.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;The udder of the cow should be cleaned with lukewarm water and colostrum should be given to the calf as soon
            as possible after birth. However, the calf must be fed colostrum within 6 hours of birth.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;If the calf has difficulty in breathing then hold the back two legs and shake them gently. If necessary,
            artificial respiration should be started by blowing through the nostrils. Otherwise the calf will die.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;The calf should be fed concentrated food, hay and green grass from 3 weeks after birth. Milk replacer and
            cuff starter can be fed if required.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Always keep the calf close to the cow. The calf bed should be made by spreading dry straw or sack in the
            barn.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Occasionally straw / sack should be changed and dried in the sun.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;The calf should be kept in a warm, soft and dry place.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;During the winter, the body of the calf should be covered with cloth or sack.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;The calf should be bathed regularly
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;The calf should be weighed regularly to help determine the calf\'s feed intake and growth rate.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;From the age of one month, calves should be given deworming drugs.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;When the calf is 4 months old, it is necessary to stop milk feeding.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;In case of calf disease, a skilled and experienced veterinarian should be consulted
        </li>
    </ol>
    ]]>
  </string>
  <string name="daily_activities_of_farm_details">
    <![CDATA[
    <h3>Farm Cleanliness</h3> <br>
    <ol>
        <li>
            &#160;Farm floor, food and water containers, dung and urine and drains adjacent to the farm house should be kept
            clean and dry regularly.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;The cow should be bathed regularly.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;The farm needs to be cleaned twice a day in the morning and in the afternoon.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Regularly change the water in the footbath mixed with potash.
        </li>
    </ol>
    <br>
    <h3>Milking</h3> <br>
    <ol>
        <li>
            &#160;Cow\'s milk should be milked once daily in the morning and afternoon at fixed times. Before milking, the
            udder of the cow and the hands of the milker should be washed thoroughly with clean water mixed with potash.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;The milking process of the cow should be completed quickly and after milking the cow should be fed dried
            straw or green grass.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Adequate rest should be given to the cows to increase the milk production of dairy cows by 15 to 20%.
        </li>
    </ol>
    <br>
    <h3>Food Supply</h3> <br>
    <ol>
        <li>
            &#160;It is necessary to provide balanced food at specific times every day as a rule.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Water containers should always have a supply of clean and pure water.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Green grass or straw should be chopped into small pieces to make it digestible.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Concentrated food must be mixed in the right proportions and it must be stored in the right way.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Regular deworming and vaccination should be applied.
        </li>
    </ol>
    ]]>
    </string>
  <string name="importance_of_public_health_details">
    <![CDATA[
    <p>Veterinary public health is a component of public health activities dedicated to the application of professional
        veterinary skills, knowledge and resources to protect and improve human health. Veterinary public health issues
        are:
    </p> <br>
    <ol>
        <li>
            &#160;Prevention of zoonotic diseases.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Safe animal food production and protection.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Farm health regulations and biosecurity.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Controlling wildlife and their environment.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Regulation of international trade in animals, animal products, animal wastes and animal foods.
        </li>
        <br>
        <li>
            &#160;Veterinary drugs (residues, antimicrobial resistance).
        </li>
    </ol>
    ]]>
  </string>
  <string name="body_length_a_to_b_inch">Body length A to B (Inch)*</string>
  <string name="body_circumference_c_inch">Body circumference C (Inch)*</string>
  <string name="click_here_for_measurement_instruction">Click here for measurement instruction</string>
  <string name="otp">OTP*</string>
  <string name="send">Send</string>
  <string name="login">Login</string>
  <string name="resend">Resend</string>
  <string name="could_not_send_otp">Could Not Send OTP</string>
  <string name="could_not_verify_otp">Could Not Verify OTP</string>
  <string name="could_not_login">Could Not Login</string>
  <string name="otp_sent_to_your_mobile_number">OTP Sent To Your Mobile Number</string>
  <string name="date_of_birth">Date Of Birth*</string>
  <string name="type_of_business_service">Type of Business / Service*</string>
  <string name="years_in_business_service">Years in Business / Service*</string>
  <string name="trade_license_number">Trade License Number</string>
  <string name="tin">TIN</string>
  <string name="website_text">Website</string>
  <string name="could_not_register_agent">Could Not Register Agent</string>
  <string name="owner_info">Owner Info</string>
  <string name="animal_info">Animal Info</string>
  <string name="disease_info">Disease Info</string>
  <string name="type_of_consultancy_support">Type Of Consultancy Support*</string>
  <string name="type_of_farm">Type Of Farm*</string>
  <string name="animals_you_have_or_plan_to_have">Number Of Animals You Have Or Plan To Have</string>
  <string name="place_of_firm">Place Of Firm</string>
  <string name="age_of_firm">Age Of Firm*</string>
  <string name="frequency_of_consultancy">Frequency Of Consultancy*</string>
  <string name="farm_info">Farm Info</string>
  <string name="farm_land_size_in_acres">Farm Land Size In Acres</string>
  <string name="housing_style">Housing Style</string>
  <string name="type_of_shades">Type Of Shades</string>
  <string name="type_of_houses">Type Of Houses</string>
  <string name="investment_in_lac">Investment In Lac</string>
  <string name="type_of_animals_or_stages_of_animals">Type Of Animals Or Stages Of Animals</string>
  <string name="type_of_feeds_available">Type Of Feeds Available</string>
  <string name="type_of_green_grasses_available">Type Of Green Grasses Available</string>
  <string name="milk_production_and_animal_number">Milk Production And Animal Number</string>
  <string name="pregnant">Pregnant</string>
  <string name="milking">Milking</string>
  <string name="heifer">Heifer</string>
  <string name="calves">Calves</string>
  <string name="male">Male</string>
  <string name="land_size_in_decimal">Land Size In Decimal</string>
  <string name="type_of_green_grass">Type Of Green Grass</string>
  <string name="soil_quality_and_texture">Soil Quality And Texture</string>
  <string name="land_status">Land Status</string>
  <string name="irrigation_system_for_grass_cultivation">Irrigation System For Grass Cultivation</string>
  <string name="grass_production_purposes">Grass Production Purposes</string>
</resources>
